Finding Aid for McHugh and Hoffman records, 1957-1995
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
McHugh and Hoffman records 1957-1995
McHugh and Hoffman.
62 linear feet
07165 Bb 2
McHugh and Hoffman, Inc., founded in 1962, was the first television news consulting firm. Their corporate papers include reports and statistical analyses concerning most major United States cities from the early 1960’s through the 1980’s.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records were acquired from Anne Bowen (donor no. 9958 ), 27 September 2007.
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The record group is open to research.
McHugh and Hoffman, the first television news consulting firm, was founded in 1962 by Philip McHugh and Peter Hoffman, formerly of Detroit's Campbell-Ewald advertising agency.
In 1962 newscasts had a very serious appearance. The work of McHugh and Hoffman found that viewers wanted more than just a laundry list of facts or a retelling of what was already available in newspapers. Instead of excessive talk of government and civic affairs, television news viewers were interested in hearing about social problems such as crime and decay. McHugh and Hoffman pioneered the "Eyewitness News" format, where reporters appeared on camera and covered a broader range of social issues. Weather and human interest content became "news you can use." In part due to the work of consultants, newscasts began to make better use of the television medium and started to include more pictorial content. The work of McHugh and Hoffman was also instrumental in introducing female anchors and reporters to the television news industry.
The research of McHugh and Hoffman, Inc. was steeped in social class analysis based upon the work of pioneering anthropologist Lloyd Warner. Many of McHugh and Hoffman's reports contain an "explanation of social class," accompanied by Warner's diamond-shaped diagrams which illustrate the stratification of class systems in the United States. The studies were based on the total population, not just an upper-middle class and upper class audience. While working class viewers found traditional television news stuffy, McHugh and Hoffman provided newsrooms with data and recommendations concerning how newscasts should respond to audience ratings. What was formerly viewed as a public service came to be an avenue for generating profit.
McHugh and Hoffman, Inc. also provided consultations for a small amount of non-news television programs, such as Sing Along With Mitch and The Mike Douglas Show.
John E. ("Jack") Bowen III became president of McHugh and Hoffman in 1985 and chairman - CEO in 1988. He died 3 March 2007.
In 1993 Market Strategies, Inc. (MSI) of Southfield, Michigan acquired McHugh and Hoffman, Inc. and the consulting firm was reincorporated as a subsidiary of MSI under a slightly different name (McHugh & Hoffman). MSI closed McHugh & Hoffman in 1999.
The McHugh and Hoffmann record group is separated into three series: Research files; Correspondence; and Business files. Research files comprises the bulk of the records and includes research reports providing summaries of viewer attitudes toward news coverage and newscasters in specific market areas. Covered are most of the major TV and radio markets in the United States and Canada. These reports also provide observations and recommendations of McHugh and Hoffman and analyses of a city's television market.
Subjects:
Bowen, John Edmund.; Hoffman, Peter.; McHugh and Hoffman.; McHugh, Philip.; Television broadcasting of news--United States.; Television viewers--United States--Attitudes.
- Research files
  The Research files series (41.5 linear ft.) is broken into the following sub-series: 1963-1980 (organized alphabetically by city); 1980-1988 (organized alphabetically by city); ABC Network News; CBS; Continuing Trends in Television; Miscellaneous Files; and NBC.
  The research files provide tremendous sociological and demographic data for most major cities in the United States. Standard reports are Viewer Attitudes Toward that city's Television Viewing, Essential Findings, Observations and Recommendations, and an analysis of that city's Television Market.
  Supplemental non-standard reports in the 1963-1980 and 1980-1988 sub-series, such as "The Personal Image of Joe Namath Among Early Evening Local News Viewers in Los Angeles" or "Habits, Motivations, and Tastes of the New York Radio Audience," are noted in the finding aid. Some studies give insight into contemporaneous regional societal issues, such as "Community Problems of the Greater Detroit Area, 1973." Occasionally raw data, focus group analyses, and interview transcripts are also included.
  The research files contain many reports which were created by third-party research firms, such as Social Research, Inc. (SRI), Bruskin Associates, the Opinion Research Corp, Gene Reilly Group, and McHugh and Hoffman's rival, Frank N. Magid Associates.
  Of particular note in the Miscellaneous Research sub-series is a 1963 report concerning Sing Along With Mitch which ultimately led to that television program's cancellation despite high ratings. Some see this event as symbolic of popular culture's shift to a younger, more rock-and-roll oriented, base. Other items include a 1981 Human Sexuality Study performed by Code Research and an early set of SRI (Social Research, Inc.) studies and proposals, dating from 1957-1963.
  In addition to the United States and Canada, McHugh and Hoffman worked with media outlets in Puerto Rico, and to a much lesser extent, England and Luxemburg.
  - 1963-1980
    - Amarillo 1968-1969 (Box 1)
    - Atlanta 1963-1975 (Box 1)
      (incl. "Attitudes of the Atlanta Negro Toward Television Programming," 1970)
    - Austin 1978-1979 (Box 2)
    - Baltimore 1968-1979 (Box 2)
    - Buffalo 1965-1978 (Box 2)
    - Buffalo 1965-1978 (cont.) (Box 3)
    - Boston 1974-1980 (Box 3)
    - Charlotte 1967-1976 (Box 3)
    - Cincinnati 1963-1966 (Box 4)
      (incl. 50-50 Club and Be Our Guest)
    - Columbus 1967-1968 (Box 4)
    - Chicago 1963-1970 (Box 4)
      (incl. "Negro Attitudes Towards Local Television in Chicago," also supplemental report; Experimental Study of the Polygraph Technique; Viewer Attitudes towards Tim Weigle, Maury Povich, Valerie Coleman, and Joel Daly; A Study of Preferences between two Weathercasters; Bruskin Associates study)
    - Chicago 1963-1970 (cont.) (Box 5)
      (incl. Sports Reporter Attitude Study; An Investigation of the Effects of Print Advertising for Network Television Programs)
    - Cleveland 1970-1979 (Box 5)
    - Cleveland 1970-1979 (cont.) (Box 6)
      (incl. Community Problems in Greater Cleveland Area, July 1975; Bruskin Associates study)
    - Dallas -- Fort Worth 1964-1979 (Box 7)
    - Dayton 1975-1979 (Box 7)
    - Dayton 1975-1979 (cont.) (Box 8)
      (incl. a Trendex Analysis by the Opinion Research Corp.)
    - Denver 1967-1979 (Box 8)
      (incl. Wasach Opinion Research Corp. survey)
    - Detroit 1964-1979 (Box 9)
      (incl. Special Issues in Detroit Television, 1963; An Evaluation of Van Patrick; Audience Flow, Early and Late Evening; A Study of Call Letter Versus Channel Number, Nielsen Detroit Audience Analysis presented by the Katz Agency, 1964; and Community Problems of the Greater Detroit Area, 1973)
    - Detroit 1964-1979 (cont.) (Box 10)
      (incl. Community Assessment Among Black TV Viewers in Detroit by Charles Richardson Associates, Inc., 1974; KPR Associates Master List of Questions, 1979)
    - Duluth 1970-1971 (Box 10)
    - Flint -- Saginaw -- Bay City 1967-1968 (Box 10)
    - Green Bay 1978 (Box 10)
    - Hartford -- New Haven 1978-1979 (Box 10)
      (incl. Viewer Attitudes Toward Jerry Taff)
    - Houston 1964-1979 (Box 10)
    - Houston 1964-1979 (cont.) (Box 11)
    - Huntsville 1971-1972 (Box 11)
    - Indianapolis 1965-1977 (Box 11)
    - Indianapolis 1965-1977 (cont.) (Box 12)
    - Kansas City 1968 (Box 12)
    - Los Angeles 1963-1978 (Box 12)
      (incl. Lifestyle Study, 1978; The Personal Image of Joe Namath Among Early Evening Local News Viewers, 1978)
    - Los Angeles 1963-1978 (cont.) (Box 13)
    - Louisville 1969-1977 (Box 13)
      (incl. A Special Study to Produce A Personality Profile of Television News Personalities by Arbitron Marketing Research)
    - Little Rock 1971-1978 (Box 13)
    - Memphis 1976-1979 (Box 13)
      (incl. Reyner and Co. Market Research and Consulting study)
    - Miami -- Palm Beach 1964-1979 (Box 13)
      (incl. KPR Associates master list of questions and price quote, 1979; Nielson News Summary)
    - Milwaukee 1963-1977 (Box 14)
    - Milwaukee 1963-1977 (cont.) (Box 15)
    - Minneapolis -- St. Paul 1966-1977 (Box 15)
      (incl. Community Problems in the Greater Minnesota St. Paul Area by Social Research, Inc.)
    - Mobile-Pensacola 1970-1977 (Box 16)
    - Nashville 1978-1979 (Box 16)
    - New Orleans 1972 (Box 16)
    - New York 1963-1975 (Box 16)
      (incl. Patterns of Radio Listening in the New York City Region)
    - New York 1963-1975 (cont.) (Box 17)
      (incl. Joan Lunden Co-Anchor Study; Characteristics, Habits, Motivations, and Tastes of the New York Radio Audience, WMC in Particular, by The Psychological Corporation)
    - New York 1963-1975 (cont.) (Box 18)
    - Oklahoma City 1969-1977 (Box 18)
    - Philadelphia 1964-1979 (Box 18)
    - Philadelphia 1964-1979 (cont.) (Box 19)
      (incl. Gene Reilly Group study)
    - Phoenix 1978-1979 (Box 19)
      (incl. KPR Assoc. blank surveys)
    - Pittsburgh 1965-1979 (Box 19)
    - Pittsburgh 1965-1979 (cont.) (Box 20)
    - Portland 1971-1976 (Box 20)
    - Raleigh-Durham 1977-1979 (Box 20)
    - Richmond 1968-1970 (Box 20)
    - Rochester 1979 (Box 21)
    - Sacramento 1965-1979 (Box 21)
    - Salt Lake City 1972-1979 (Box 21)
      (incl. Bureau of Government and Opinion Research, Utah State University study)
    - San Antonio 1973-1977 (Box 21)
      (incl. Trendex Special Study, Newscasters, Weathermen, and Sports Announcers)
    - San Diego 1978-1979 (Box 21)
    - San Diego 1978-1979 (cont.) (Box 22)
      (incl. Viewer Attitudes Towards Maury Povich and Valerie Coleman)
    - San Francisco 1969-1979 (Box 22)
    - San Juan, Puerto Rico 1969 (Box 22)
    - Savannah 1979 (Box 23)
      (incl. TV News in the Coastal Empire, Frank N. Magid Assoc., Inc.)
    - Seattle -- Tacoma 1970-1977 (Box 23)
    - South Bend 1978 (Box 23)
      (incl. South Bend Selection Research, Inc. study)
    - Spokane County 1966 (Box 23)
    - St. Louis 1963-1966 (Box 23)
    - Syracuse -- Buffalo 1978-1979 (Box 24)
    - Toledo 1962-1974 (Box 24)
      (incl. telephone study notes, 1964; Community Problems in the Greater Toledo Area, 1973)
    - Toledo 1962-1974 (cont.) (Box 25)
    - Tucson 1971-1979 (Box 25)
    - Tulsa 1976 (Box 25)
    - Washington D.C. 1967-1979 (Box 25)
      (incl. Mediatrac Local TV News Viewer Opinion Study)
    - West Palm Beach (Box 26)
  - 1980-1988
    - Abilene 1982 (Box 26)
    - Atlanta 1981-1988 (Box 26)
    - Boston 1980-1982 (Box 26)
      (incl. notes and raw data)
    - Chicago 1980-1982 (Box 27)
      (incl. Chicago Lifestyle Study: Factors Inhibiting and Facilitating News Viewing, 1982)
    - Cleveland 1980-1981 (Box 27)
    - Dallas 1980-1983 (Box 27)
    - Dayton 1980-1981 (Box 27)
    - Denver 1983-1984 (Box 27)
    - Detroit 1980-1984 (Box 28)
      (incl. Detroit Lifestyle Study; Sensationalism in Viewer Thinking, Early News Viewing and Potential News Teams; Interview Guide)
    - Green Bay 1980-1984 (Box 28)
    - Green Bay 1980-1984 (cont.) (Box 29)
      (incl. interview raw data and forms)
    - Houston 1980-1984 (Box 29)
    - Huntsville 1980 (Box 29)
    - Lexington 1981-1984 (Box 29)
    - Little Rock 1982 (Box 30)
    - Los Angeles 1980-1984 (Box 30)
      (incl. Lifestyle Study: Audience Clusters; Theatre Study of Sportscast Concepts, Lifestyles, Needs, Situations, and Moods Which Facilitate or Impede Early Evening Local Newscast Viewing; The Place of Television News in Viewer Lifestyles; Lifestyle Orientations Toward Cable TV Among Subscribers and Disconnects)
    - Louisville 1981-1984 (Box 30)
    - Memphis 1980 (Box 30)
    - Miami 1981-1984 (Box 31)
      (incl. Miami Focus Group Report)
    - Midland -- Odessa, Texas 1984 (Box 31)
    - Milwaukee 1982-1983 (Box 31)
    - Mobile-Pensacola 1980 (Box 31)
    - New York 1980-1984 (Box 31)
      (incl. Lifestyle Study)
    - New York 1980-1984 (cont.) (Box 32)
      (incl. A Report on Four Focus Group Sessions, Blanks Surveys, Raw Data, and Correspondence)
    - Omaha 1980 (Box 33)
    - Phoenix 1981-1983 (Box 33)
      (incl. blank forms of tables)
    - Philadelphia 1983 (Box 33)
      (incl. Perceptions of Change in KYW-TV's Imagery)
    - Pittsburgh 1982 (Box 33)
      (incl. Role of TV News Viewer Lifestyles)
    - Portland 1982-1984 (Box 33)
    - Rochester 1983-1984 (Box 34)
    - Sacramento 1980 (Box 34)
    - Salt Lake City 1980-1981 (Box 34)
      (incl. Female Newscaster and Weathercaster Candidate Research; KTVX Focus Group by Dan Jones and Assoc.)
    - San Diego 1980-1984 (Box 34)
    - San Francisco 1980-1984 (Box 34)
    - San Francisco 1980-1984 (cont.) (Box 35)
      (incl. Lifestyle Study; Audience Segmentation Study)
    - Savannah 1981-1983 (Box 35)
    - Seattle 1980-1983 (Box 35)
    - South Bend 1981-1982 (Box 36)
    - Springfield, Mass. 1981-1983 (Box 36)
    - St. Louis 1981 (Box 36)
    - Tampa 1980-1983 (Box 36)
      (incl. Verbatim Responses; Types of Newscast Viewers Chart)
    - Toledo 1981-1983 (Box 36)
    - Tulsa 1980-1984 (Box 36)
    - Washington DC 1980-1984 (Box 37)
      (incl. Lifestyle Study; Telephone Study of Principal Market Personalities and Station Imagery, blank surveys, raw data)
  - ABC Network News
    - Audience Studies, Inc.
      - Network News Comparison Study 1973 (Box 37)
        (7 volumes, Volume I missing)
      - The Harry Reasoner Report, ASI Audience Reaction Tests 1973 (Box 37)
    - Lieberman Research, Inc., Basic Attitude Surveys 1973-1974 (Box 38)
    - McCollum, Spielman, and Company, Inc. Communications Research
      - ABC News Team Evaluations (Box 38)
    - McHugh and Hoffman
      - 1975 Research Proposal (Box 38)
      - 1976 Research and Consulting Objectives (Box 38)
      - ABC Owned Stations Division 1974-1975 (Box 38)
      - Children's Attitudes Toward Rainbow Sundae / Over Seven, 1975 (Box 38)
      - Essential Findings and Recommendations 1969, 1970, 1972, 1974 (Box 38)
      - Monitoring Report, Network Television 1974 (Box 38)
      - Network News Comparison Study, Volume I 1973 (Box 38)
        (subsequent volumes missing)
      - Network News Images 1974 (Box 38)
      - Network News Election Coverage 1974 (Box 38)
      - The Harry Reasoner Report 1973 (Box 38)
      - Public Attitudes Toward Television and Television News 1976 (Box 38)
      - Viewer Attitudes Toward Network Newscasts 1972 (Box 38)
    - Social Research, Inc.
      - Network Television Newscasts, A Research Proposal 1975 (Box 38)
  - CBS
    - Analysis of the Columbia Television Stations 1963-1964 (Box 38)
    - Candid Camera and What's My Line, 1966 (Box 38)
    - Evening Magazine, 1977 (Box 38)
    - Huntley-Brinkley Report 1964 (Box 38)
    - Proposals 1962 (Box 38)
    - Summary of CBS Television Systems Markets 1963-1965 (Box 38)
  - Continuing Trends in Television
    - 1962 (Box 39)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 39)
    - 1965 (Box 39)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 39)
    - 1976 (Box 39)
    - 1977 (Box 39)
    - 1983 (Box 40)
      (incl. raw data)
  - Miscellaneous Research
    - ASI 1986 (Box 40)
    - Cable 1981, 1993 (Box 40)
    - Canadian Advertising Study 1966 (Box 40)
    - Canadian Radio 1969-1973 (Box 40)
    - Code Research, Human Sexuality Study 1981 (Box 40)
    - Directory of News Management and Producers 1985 (Box 40)
    - Fields Television Investment Group, Special Report On The Relationship Between Local Television Programming and Television Station's Receivers 1986 (Box 40)
    - Health News Report Raw Data, Peter J. Hart Research 1990 (Box 40)
    - How People Use Television Promotion, Social Research Incorporated 1963 (Box 40)
    - An Interest-Based Segmentation Study of Television Audiences, AAPOR Conference 1978 (Box 41)
    - KPR Associates, Inc., Marketing Research (Box 41)
    - McGavern-Guild Co., Images and Attitudes of four Radio Station Representatives 1964 (Box 41)
    - The Mike Douglas Show, 1974-1975 (Box 41)
    - Minority Recruiting, Development, and Training (Box 41)
    - Montreal, Canada, A Study of Viewer Attitudes 1966, 1976 (Box 41)
    - News Consultant Image Study 1986 (Box 41)
    - Newspapers 1985 (Box 41)
    - Northeast Airlines Advertising Awareness 1966 (Box 41)
    - J.C. Penney, Image and Status, A Pilot Study 1964 (Box 41)
    - The Perception Analyzer Device Advertisement (Box 41)
    - Relations Between Gratifications Sought and Obtained. A Study of Television News 1980 (Box 41)
    - The Rundown, Television News Newsletter 1994-1995 (Box 41)
    - Sing Along With Mitch, 1963 (Box 41)
    - SRI (Social Research, Inc.) Studies and Proposals 1957-1963 (Box 41)
      (incl. Women and Department Store Advertising, 1957)
    - Storer Cable Stations / Storer International 1962, 1967, 1982 (Box 42)
    - Television Audience Research and News Programming Issues 1983-1984 (Box 42)
    - VALS 1983 (Box 42)
    - What's My Line, Viewer Attitudes, 1966 (Box 42)
    - Women, Health, and the Media (Box 42)
    - A. J. Wood Research Corp., A Study of Television Viewers and Their Viewing Habits 1965 (Box 42)
  - NBC
    - The Tonight Show, Evaluation, Summary, Conclusions, and Recommendations, 1963 (Box 42)
- Correspondence
  The Correspondence series (10.5 linear ft.) is organized by the collection's original order and is broken into the following sub-series: 1966-1983; 1983; 1984; 1985-1989; Canadian Correspondence; England; Storer Cable; and Miscellaneous. In addition to correspondence with television news departments, many files also contain additional research and monitoring reports. The Storer Cable files include a 1969 study titled Sex and Violence on Television: A Viewer's Reaction.
  - 1966-1983
    - KABC Los Angeles 1981-1982 (Box 42)
    - KCST San Diego 1982 (Box 42)
    - KDFW Dallas 1980-1981 (Box 42)
    - KGO San Francisco 1976-1982 (Box 43)
    - KGMH Denver 1975-1980 (Box 43)
    - KING Seattle 1983 (Box 43)
    - KMTV Omaha 1980-1982 (Box 43)
    - KOKA Pittsburgh 1981-1982 (Box 43)
    - KOOL Phoenix 1982 (Box 43)
    - KOTV Tulsa 1981 (Box 43)
    - KRBC Abilene 1982 (Box 44)
    - KTHV Little Rock 1980-1982 (Box 44)
    - KTRK Houston 1981-1982 (Box 44)
    - KTVI St. Louis 1981 (Box 44)
    - KTVX Salt Lake City 1982 (Box 44)
    - KXTV Sacramento 1980-1981 (Box 44)
    - KYW Philadelphia 1981 (Box 44)
    - WABC New York City 1976-1982 (Box 44)
    - WAFF Huntsville 1981 (Box 44)
    - WAGA Atlanta 1981-1982 (Box 44)
    - WBZ Boston 1981-1982 (Box 44)
    - WCBD Charleston 1982 (Box 45)
    - WCCO Minneapolis 1981 (Box 45)
    - WCKT Miami 1980-1982 (Box 45)
    - WFLA Tampa 1978-1981 (Box 45)
    - WGXA Macon 1982 (Box 45)
    - WHAS Louisville 1980-1982 (Box 45)
    - WISN Milwaukee 1966-1980 (Box 45)
    - WITI Milwaukee 1977-1982 (Box 45)
    - WJLA Washington, D.C. 1978-1982 (Box 45)
    - WJLA Washington, D.C. 1978-1982 (cont.) (Box 46)
    - WJKS Jacksonville 1977-1983 (Box 46)
    - WJKW Cleveland 1982 (Box 46)
    - WJZ Baltimore 1981-1983 (Box 46)
    - WKRG Mobile 1982 (Box 46)
    - WKYC Cleveland 1981 (Box 46)
    - WLUK Green Bay 1982 (Box 46)
    - WLS Chicago 1981-1982 (Box 46)
    - WNEM Saginaw 1977 (Box 46)
    - WOC-TV Davenport, Iowa 1965-1982 (Box 46)
    - WOKR Rochester 1965-1982 (Box 46)
    - WOTV Grand Rapids, Mich. 1967-1983 (Box 46)
    - WOWT Omaha 1974-1981 (Box 46)
    - WPEC West Palm Beach 1967-1983 (Box 46)
    - WROC Rochester 1981-1982 (Box 46)
    - WSBT South Bend 1981-1982 (Box 46)
    - WSOC Charlotte 1982 (Box 46)
    - WSPD Toledo 1978 (Box 46)
    - WSTM Syracuse 1981 (Box 46)
    - WTHR Indianapolis 1981-1983 (Box 46)
    - WTMJ Milwaukee 1979 (Box 46)
    - WTNH New Haven, Conn. 1980-1981 (Box 46)
    - WTOC Savannah 1981 (Box 46)
    - WUTV Buffalo 1982 (Box 46)
    - WXYZ Detroit 1978-1982 (Box 47)
  - 1983
    - KABC Los Angeles (Box 47)
    - KCST San Diego (Box 47)
    - KDKA Pittsburgh (Box 47)
    - KGAN Cedar Rapids (Box 47)
    - KGO San Francisco (Box 47)
    - KING Seattle (Box 47)
    - KMTV Omaha (Box 47)
    - KRBC Abilene (Box 47)
    - KTHV Little Rock (Box 47)
    - KTRK Houston (Box 47)
    - KTSP Phoenix (Box 47)
    - KTVO Ottumwa, Iowa -- Kirksville, Missouri (Box 47)
    - WABC New York City (Box 47)
    - WAGA Atlanta (Box 47)
    - WBZ Boston (Box 47)
    - WCBD Charleston (Box 47)
    - WEAU Eu Claire, Wisc. (Box 47)
    - WECA Tallahassee (Box 47)
    - WFLA Tampa (Box 47)
    - WGAN Portland (Box 48)
    - WGGB Springfield, Mass. (Box 48)
    - WHAS Louisville (Box 48)
    - WITI Milwaukee (Box 48)
    - WJKS Jacksonville (Box 48)
    - WJKW Cleveland (Box 48)
    - WJLA Washington D.C. (Box 48)
    - WKCT Miami (Box 48)
    - WKRG Mobile (Box 48)
    - WLS Chicago (Box 48)
    - WLUC Marquette, Mich. (Box 48)
    - WLUK Green Bay (Box 48)
    - WOKR Rochester (Box 48)
    - WSAV Savannah (Box 48)
    - WSBT South Bend (Box 48)
    - WSOC Charlotte (Box 48)
    - WTKR Norfolk (Box 48)
    - WTVG Toledo (Box 48)
  - 1984
    - KABC Los Angeles (Box 48)
    - KCST San Diego (Box 48)
    - KDFW Dallas (Box 48)
    - KDKA Pittsburgh (Box 48)
    - KGAN Cedar Rapids (Box 48)
    - KGO San Francisco (Box 48)
    - KGO San Francisco (cont.) (Box 49)
    - KING Seattle (Box 49)
    - KMGH Denver (Box 49)
    - KMTV Omaha (Box 49)
    - KRBC Abilene (Box 49)
    - KSTP Phoenix (Box 49)
    - KTRK Houston (Box 49)
    - KTUL Tulsa (Box 49)
    - KTRK Houston (Box 49)
    - WAGA Atlanta (Box 49)
    - WBZ Boston (Box 49)
    - WCBD Charleston (Box 49)
    - WEAU Eu Claire, Wisconsin (Box 49)
    - WGME Portland (Box 49)
    - WHAS Louisville (Box 49)
    - WITI Milwaukee (Box 49)
    - WJKS Jacksonville (Box 49)
    - WJKW Cleveland (Box 49)
    - WJLA Washington D.C. (Box 50)
    - WLUC Marquette, Mich. (Box 50)
    - WLUK Green Bay (Box 50)
    - WORK Rochester (Box 50)
    - WSVN Miami (Box 50)
    - WXFL Tampa (Box 50)
    - WXYZ Detroit (Box 50)
  - 1985-1989
    - KCST San Diego (Box 50)
    - KDFW Dallas (Box 50)
    - KGAN Cedar Rapids (Box 50)
    - KGGM Albuquerque (Box 51)
    - KGMH Denver (Box 51)
    - KGO San Francisco (Box 51)
    - KITV Honolulu (Box 51)
    - KMTV Omaha (Box 52)
    - KSBW Salinas -- Monterey (Box 52)
    - KTBC Austin (Box 52)
    - KTHV Little Rock (Box 52)
    - KTPX Midland, Texas (Box 52)
    - KTRK Houston (Box 52)
    - KTSP Phoenix (Box 52)
    - KTVL Tulsa (Box 52)
    - KTVI St. Louis (Box 53)
    - KTVK Phoenix (Box 53)
    - KWTV Oklahoma City (Box 53)
    - WAGA Atlanta (Box 53)
    - WEVV Ft. Myers (Box 53)
    - WGGB Springfield, Mass. (Box 53)
    - WGME Portland (Box 53)
    - WICS Springfield, Ill. (Box 53)
    - WITI Milwaukee (Box 53)
    - WJZ Baltimore (Box 53)
    - WKAQ San Juan, Puerto Rico (Box 53)
    - WKYC Cleveland (Box 53)
    - WKYT Lexington (Box 54)
    - WLII San Juan, Puerto Rico (Box 54)
    - WLNE Providence (Box 54)
    - WLUK Green Bay (Box 54)
    - WLS Chicago (Box 54)
    - WLWT Cincinnati (Box 54)
    - WMAQ Chicago (Box 54)
    - WNEV Boston (Box 54)
    - WNEV Boston (cont.) (Box 55)
    - WNMT Kalamazoo (Box 55)
    - WPCQ Charlotte (Box 55)
    - WPEC West Palm Beach (Box 55)
    - WSAZ Charleston (Box 55)
    - WSBT South Bend (Box 55)
    - WSOC Charlotte (Box 55)
    - WSVN Miami (Box 55)
    - WTHR Indianapolis (Box 56)
    - WTKR Norfolk (Box 56)
    - WTTG Washington D.C. (Box 56)
    - WTVC Chattanooga (Box 56)
    - WTVG Toledo (Box 56)